trafficcaptain.com 2017-06-15

# Trafficpartner

## This website is operated by

TrafficPartner B.V.  
Frans Erensstraat 14 A  
5921VG Venlo  
The Netherlands  
Tel: +31 7720610 31  
Fax: +31 7720614 35  
E-Mail: [info@trafficpartner.com](mailto:info@trafficpartner.com)

**Personal data**  
Personal data means information by which a person may be identified, i.e., data that can be matched to an individual. This includes names, email addresses or telephone numbers, but also data concerning preferences, hobbies, memberships or previously visited websites.

Only data that are anonymous, i.e. are stored without reference to a specific individual (for instance the number of visits to a particular website), do not qualify as personal data. If there is a legitimate cause for concern, please contact the party responsible for the site immediately in writing. Where any infringement of rights is detected, the content in question will be removed from the site without delay.

**Collection of access data**  
The host of this offer collects data on each single access to the offer. Such data are stored anonymously, without reference to specific individuals. Access data includes:

• the name of the visited website,  
• the file, date and time of the visit,  
• the data load that was transferred,  
• a download report,  
• the browser used, including its version,  
• the user’s operating system,  
• the referrer URL (the previously visited site) and the referring provider (such as T-Online),  
• and the data requested from the host’s server.

The host will use the log file data without identification of the user, exclusively for purposes of statistical analyses for operating and optimizing the offer. However, the host reserves the right to subsequently check the log file data if there is concrete, legitimate evidence to suspect unlawful use.

**Collection and use of personal data**  
Personal data will be collected and used by the host only as permitted by law or authorized by the user. A user using the service normally will be aware of the data that are stored, for example the name, email address and message when using a contact or comment form.

**Contact**  
When users initiate contact with the Operator (e.g. via e-mail or via a contact form), the user’s data will be stored for the purpose of handling the inquiry and in the event that questions arise later. The data will never be forwarded to any third party. Neither will the data be matched with other data that might have been acquired via other components of our website.

**Warnings, data integrity**  
The host has taken organizational, contractual and technical safety precautions to ensure compliance with the applicable data protection laws. However, users should be aware that the access to publicly available data cannot be fully controlled. Sensitive information, such as intimate details, illnesses, religious views or similar should therefore not be published at all. Users who nevertheless decide to publish such details should be aware that their disclosure on the internet often is irreversible.

**Data transfer to third parties**  
User data will be transferred to third parties only as permitted by law or authorized by the user. Without the user’s consent, the personal data of a user will under no circumstances be sold or transferred to any third party for purposes of advertising or setting up of user profiles.

**Data transfer to third parties abroad**  
Any transfer of data to third parties abroad will be strictly subject to the applicable laws. Data will be transferred to non-Member States of the European Union or to other contracting states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area only if such countries offer an adequate level of protection within the meaning of the German Data Protection Act. Third parties based in the USA will be assumed to offer an adequate level of protection if they have agreed to comply with the Safe Harbour agreement (such as Google).

*Cookies*  
The host uses cookies in connection with the offer. Cookies are small files that are stored on the user’s computer and save information for the host. Temporary cookies will be deleted after the browser is closed, while permanent cookies are maintained for a predefined period of time and provide the stored information when the user revisits the offer.

Cookies are used to facilitate the use of the service. For example, a cookie saves the user’s login status so the user does not have to log in anew each time.

Further, cookies are used for statistical or marketing purposes to survey the use of the offer. The data are collected anonymously or by using pseudonyms, which means the data are stored without identification of the users. Such cookies are provided by the host or by third parties (such as advertising partners).

Users may at any time object to any such use of their data by notice to the contact details set out at the end of this privacy policy. If the host cannot be reasonably expected, for technical or economic reasons, to suspend any such data processing for individual users, the host may terminate the user relationship with the user.

Users are able to control the use of cookies. Most browsers offer an option to restrict or fully refuse any storing of cookies. The host seeks to arrange the offer so that no cookies are necessary. Users are advised, however, that the use and in particular user friendliness may be impaired if no cookies are accepted.

**Google Adsense**  
Where Google AdSense, a web advertising service offered by Google Inc., USA (‘Google’), is used for placing advertisements through text ads or banners, the user’s browser will store a cookie provided by Google or a third party. The information stored in the cookie may be collected, used and transferred by Google or third parties. Further, Google AdSense also uses web beacons to collect information. Web beacons are small, invisible graphics used by Google to document and analyze actions such as website traffic.

The information collected as described above on the user’s use of the offer is transferred to and stored on a Google server located in the USA. Google uses the collected information to analyze user behaviour with regard to the AdSense ads. Google may transfer such information to third parties, where required by law or where third parties process such data under contract for Google. Google will not associate the IP address with other data stored by Google. In using this website the user agrees to the processing of the data collected on the user by Google, in the manner and for the purposes described above.

Users may restrict or refuse the collection of information by Google by changing the cookie settings in their browser (see the section on ‘Cookies’).

*Google Analytics*  
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (‘Google’). Google Analytics uses ‘cookies’, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. You can prevent Google from detecting a cookie that is generated because of and related to your usage of this website (including your IP address) as well as processing of these data by downloading and installing this browser plugin: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

**Facebook Social Plugins**  
This offer may make use of the social plugins (‘plugins’) of the social network facebook.com operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (‘Facebook’). The plugins are labelled with one of the Facebook logos (white ‘f’ on a blue tile or ‘thumbs up’ sign) or the addition ‘Facebook Social Plugin’. For a list and the appearance of the Facebook Social Plugins, please see <http://developers.facebook.com/plugins>.

If a user visits a website of this offer that contains any such plugin, the user’s browser will set up a direct connection to the Facebook servers. The plugin content is transmitted by Facebook directly to the user’s browser and incorporated into the website by the browser. As the host has no control over the amount of data collected by Facebook by way of the plugin, users are informed of the status as known to the host: Via the incorporated plugin Facebook is provided with the information that the user has accessed the relevant site of our internet presence. If you are logged in at Facebook, Facebook is able to match the visit to the user’s Facebook account. If the user interacts with the plugin, e.g. activates the “I Like” button or posts a comment, the information is transmitted directly to Facebook by the user’s browser and stored by Facebook. If the user is not a Facebook member Facebook may nevertheless identify and store the user’s IP address. For the purpose and extent of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as your related rights and setup options for protecting your privacy, please see the Facebook privacy policy: http://www.facebook.com/policy.php

Users who are Facebook members but do not wish Facebook to collect user data through our internet presence to connect them with the users’ Facebook data, have to log off from Facebook before visiting our internet sites. For the purpose and extent of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as your related rights and setup options for protecting your privacy, please see the Facebook privacy policy: http://www.facebook.com/policy.php

Users who are Facebook members but do not wish Facebook to collect user data through our internet presence to connect them with the users’ Facebook data, have to log off from Facebook before visiting our internet sites.

*Collection and use of data by third parties*  
Third parties may offer services in connection with our offer as well. These may be incorporated third party applications, banners or links. Any such offers will be clearly marked as third party offers for users and are not subject to the host’s privacy policy but to the privacy policy of the respective third parties.  
Objections, data amendments, correction, updates  
Users may contact the host at any time and request the amendment, correction or deletion of their data. Further, users may object to the setup of pseudonymous user profiles for advertising and market research. In any such event the host will have the right to exclude the user from using the service. In particular but without limitation, this right applies where individual exceptions are impossible for technical or economic reasons.

**Amendments to the privacy policy**  
The host reserves the right to amend the privacy policy to accommodate changes in legislation or modifications to the service or data processing operations. Users will be notified of any amendment to the privacy policy in an appropriate context.

**Contact, questions, queries and suggestions**  
For information, objections, questions, suggestions and proposals concerning the privacy policy users may contact the host at any time.
